New York State Conference of Local Mental Hygiene Directors; Records apap315
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Managed Care and Special Needs Plans, 1991-2000; Undated; 6; 2.0 cu. ft.
  - "Overcoming Barriers to Effective Use of Behavioral Health Care Data: Opportunities for State and Local Collaboration", 1999 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 26)
  - "Parity in Financing Mental Health Services: Managed Care Effects on Cost, Access, and Quality", 1998 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 27)
  - Planning documents- Office of Mental Health, Westchester County, 1999 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 28)
  - "Preparing for Managed Care Challenges" forum packet, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 29)
  - Proposal for the Development and Implementation of a Statewide Managed Care Action Plan, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 30)
  - Proposal to Establish Uniform Standards for Mental Health Managed Care Referral and Billing Processes, 1995 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 31)
  - Report on Rate Methodology Underlying New York City SNP Requests for Proposals, 2000 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 32)
  - Request for Information responses- Special needs plans, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 33)
  - Revised Medicaid waiver, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 34)
  - Rochester Medicare Demonstration Project, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 35)
  - Senate- Assembly: Act to amend mental hygiene law, 1993 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 36)
  - Special needs plans legislation, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 37)
  - Special needs plans- Powerpoint overview, 1999; Undated (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 38)
  - Special needs plans regional forum, Batavia, 1998 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 39)
  - Specs- Consultant managed care action plan, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 40)
  - State behavioral health headlines, Vol. I #27 (SAMHSA managed care), 2000 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 41)
  - State of New York Office of the Comptroller- Audit of state mental health services and response of agency officials, 1993 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 42)
  - Steering committee conference calls- Medicaid managed care, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 43)
  - Strategic planning for managed care/CHPS Consulting, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 44-45)
  - Survey results of technical assistance needs for implementing managed care within communities, Undated (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 46)
  - Technical assistance- Survey and finance issues, 1998; Undated (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 47)
- Subject Files, 1985-2008; Undated; 7; 5.4 cu. ft.
  The subject files house documents of long-term value that do not belong to the Conference’s other record series. There are correspondence and memo files of specific members of the group, such as Peter Freed (counsel) and Gerry Landsberg (New York University), background on shared staff issues, and information on partnerships with the New York State divisions of alcohol abuse and chemical dependency as well as state housing committees. Researchers will also find documents pertaining to consolidation of services and positions over the years, particularly in the 1990s. Additionally, there are manuals, booklets, and conference materials about disaster preparedness in the mental health profession. Most of the collection’s photographs are also located in this series, with the exception of the Commission on the 21st Century images which are in Series #5.
  - 2002 Regulatory review workgroup, 1994; 2001; 2002-2003 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - 2002 Regulatory review workgroup (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - 2002 Regulatory review workgroup, 2002-2003 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Adult homes- Issues and recommendations, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Adult homes workgroup, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Annual report: Serving the mental health needs of young offenders, 2000 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - "Assessing the nature and prevalence of mentally ill in Suffolk County's criminal justice system", 2000 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - "At the Crossroads" Reinvestment/realignment report and supplementary materials, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Bond, Schoeneck, and King, Attorneys at Law, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Committee on Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Developmental Disabilities: "Broken Promises, Broken Lives" status report, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Committees and task forces, 1996; Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Community service boards: Training, 1990-1992; 1995 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Community services block grant- Management plan, 2000 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Comprehensive Psychiatric Emergency Programs, 2000 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Conference goals and missions- overview packet, 2000 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Consolidated fiscal reform (CFR), 1993-1994 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Consultant contract: Tremblay Associates, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - "The Courage to Change: A Guide for Communities to Create Integrated Services", 1999 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - "Cost of Addictive and Mental Disorders and Effectiveness of Treatment", Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - County charges- Medicaid, 2003-2004 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - County Programs, 2000 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - County reinvestment, 1993; 1997-1998 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - County reinvestment surveys, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Department of Health licensing verification edits, 2001-2002 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Director of Community Services and Commissioner of Social Services- Serving a dual role, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Director of Community Services credentials and qualifications, 1989; 1991-1992 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Director of Community Services credentials and qualifications, 1992 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Directory: New York State Conference of Local Mental Hygiene Directors, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Disaster planning: All-hazards planning worksheet, 2003 November (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Disaster planning:Communicating in a Crisis- Risk Communication Guidelines for Public Officials, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Disaster planning: Data collection toolkit, Undated (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Disaster planning: Department of Health and Human Services, 2002 June (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Disaster planning:Developing Culture Competence, 2003 (Box 1 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Disaster planning:Disaster Mental Health Response Handbook, Undated (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Disaster planning:Disaster Mental Health Services, 1997 September (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3-4)
  - Disaster planning:Disaster Mental Health Services I- Participant's Workbook, Undated (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Disaster planning: Draft-"Mental Health and Mass Violence" best practices report, 2002 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Disaster planning: Federation of Families for Children's Mental Health- "Claiming Children", 2003 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Disaster planning: Field manual for mental health and human service workers in major disasters, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Disaster planning: Grief counseling resource guide, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Disaster planning: Hurricane Katrina reception plan, Undated (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Disaster planning: "Impact of September 11, 2001- Events on substance use and mental health in the New York area", 2003 January (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Disaster planning: "Lessons from Disaster- A Conference and Conversation", SUNY New Paltz, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Disaster planning:Mental Health All-Hazards Disaster Planning Guidance, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13-14)
  - Disaster planning:Mental Health Emergency Response Plan, Undated (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Disaster planning:Mental Health Interventions following Major Disasters- A Guide, 2002 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Disaster planning: NYS Office of Mental Health Incident Command System- Powerpoint slides, Undated (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Disaster planning: NYSPA notebook, 2001 November-December (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Disaster planning:Preparing for the Psychological Consequences of Terrorism, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Disaster planning: Project Liberty training presentations (Powerpoint slides), 2002 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Disaster planning:Psychological Issues for Children and Adolescents in Disasters, 2004 February (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Disaster planning: State mental health authorities' response to terrorism, 2004 February (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Disaster planning: Training manuals, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Disaster planning:When a Person with Mental Illness is Arrested- How to Help, 2001 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Disproportionate Share Hospitals (DSH) and Medicaid, 1997; 2002-2003 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Division of Alcoholism and Alcohol Abuse: Bulletin, Vol. II #7, 1991 October (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Division of Alcoholism and Alcohol Abuse: Correspondence, newsletters, and press releases, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Division of Alcohol Abuse: Director's office, 1991 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Division of Alcoholism and Alcohol Abuse: Family support communities, 1990 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Division of Substance Abuse services: Consolidation with Division of Alcoholism and Alcohol Abuse, 1990-1993 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Division of Substance Abuse Services: Correspondence and accompanying materials, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Division of Substance Abuse Services: Director's office, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Division of Substance Abuse Services: "Executive budget recommendations", 1991-1992 (Box 2 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Division of Substance Abuse Services: Merger with Division of Alcoholism and Alcohol Abuse, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Division of Substance Abuse Services: Merger with Division of Alcoholism and Alcohol Abuse Services- legislation, 1988 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Division of Substance Abuse Services: Rate-setting proposal, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Dornan, Douglas- Retirement speech, 1994 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - "Double Jeopardy: Persons with mental illnesses in the criminal justice system", 1995 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Dungan, Stephen- Conference chair materials, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - "Families Together" newsletter, Fall issue, 2002 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Fingerprinting- Chapter 575 of Laws of 2004, information meeting, 2004-2006 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Forensic Mental Health Conference, Buffalo, 2001 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Forensic Mental Health Conference, Kingston, 2000 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Forensic Mental Health Conference, Lake Placid, 2001 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Forensic Mental Health Regional Conference, Long Island, 2001 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Forensic site visits, Undated (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Forensics: Criminal justice and prison issues, 1994; 1999-2001; Undated (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Forensics: General information, 2001 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Forensics: Risk assessment training, 2000 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Freed, Peter- Correspondence, 1989; 1991-1994 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Freed, Peter- Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Freed, Peter- Counsel on mental health initiatives, 1991; 1994-1997 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Governor's program bill #206, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Gowanda consolidation plan testimony, 1991 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Healthcare: 32-day limit on Medicaid, 1985; 1992 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Healthcare: 32-day limit on Medicaid, 1992 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Healthcare Recruitment and Retention Act, 2002 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996, 2000 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - The Innovation group- background packet, 1987-1991 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Jail diversion: Knowledge development and application program, Undated (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Jail diversion survey, 2001 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Jail/mental health symposium surveys, 2002 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Landsberg, Gerry: Intensive case management, 1989; 1991-1992; 1998 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Long-term care in New York State- task force report from governor's office, 1993 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Mandate relief workgroup, 1994; 1950-2008 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - MDI Associates, 1994 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Medicaid community support programs- notes, reports, letters, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Medicaid community support programs- notes, reports, letters, 2002 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Medicaid community support programs- rate calculation sheets, 1997 August (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Medicaid community support programs- rate calculation sheets, 1997 December (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Medicaid community support programs- regulations/ conference comments, 1997-1998 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Medicaid managed care committees, 1996; Undated (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Medicaid- state takeover, 1989; 1991; 1993 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Mental health care in prison- background materials, Undated (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Mental health court legislation, 2000 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - National Association of County Behavioral Health Directors, 1999 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - National GAINS Center, 1996-1999; Undated (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - National GAINS Center and Rensselaer County Department of Mental Health, 2000; Undated (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - New York State Division of Housing and community housing renewal, 1990; 1992 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - New York State Division of Housing and community housing renewal, 1993 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13-14)
  - New York State Division of Housing and community housing renewal, 1994 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - New York State comprehensive housing affordability strategy, 1992; 1993 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - New York State Comptroller's office- Edward V. Regan, 1990-1991 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - New York State Comptroller's office- Edward V. Regan, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - New York State Office of Advocate for the Disabled, 1991 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - New York State Sheriffs' Association Institute- Jail administrator's training conference, 2000 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - NYS Division of Probation and Correctional Alternatives annual report, 1998 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - NYS Office of Mental Health: Leaders of the Mental Health Response Training Program, 2003 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - OASAS booklet: "Collaboration- OASAS and the Criminal Justice System", 2001 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - OASAS booklet: "Substance Abuse Treatment for Persons in the Criminal Justice System", 2001 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Office of Mental Health Assisted Outpatient Treatment implementation plan, 1999 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Office of Mental Health Blueprint- 21st Century health care, 2000 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Office of Mental Health: Flexible Funding Plan and Federal Single Audit Act, 1996; 1997 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Office of Mental Health: High needs regulations, 2000 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Office of Mental Health: Involuntary commitment, 1991; 1993 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Olmstead Decision, 2001-2002 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Pataki transition team, 1994 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Photo directories from NYSCLMHD website, 2004-2005 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Photographs, mainly unidentified- Includes NYSCLHMD 10th anniversary and photo negatives, Undated (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - "Planning and Implementing Effective Mental Health Services in Jail", Undated (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Policy Research Associates: Organizational overview and recent projects, Undated (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Press clippings, 1994-1995; 2004; Undated (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Press contacts, 1990; 1992 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - "Prisons and Jails: Hospitals of Last Resort", 1999 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - "Progress report on New York State's Public Mental Health System"/Shared caseload workgroups, 2001 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Regional forensics conferences, 2000-2001 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Reinvestment- Census reduction, 1994-1995 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Reinvestment extender, 1997-1998 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Reinvestment guidelines and reports, 1994 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Reinvestment reporting- Office of Mental Health, 1995 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Report of the Adult Care Facilities Workgroup to Commissioner Antonia Novello, 2002 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Risk management workshop, New York City, 2001 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation: "Building Healthy Systems for People with Chronic Illness", 1996 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Shared staff: Aggregate statewide costs, 2000-2002 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Shared staff: Assisted Outpatient Treatment budget requests by county, A-N, 1999 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Shared staff: Assisted Outpatient Treatment budget requests by county, O-Y, 1999 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Shared staff: Background and legislation, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Shared staff: Data summary charts, 1999 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Shared staff: Estimated numbers of clients affected by loss of staff, 1999 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Shared staff: Impact by county, A-E, 1999 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Shared staff: Impact by county, G-W, 1999 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Shared staff: Impact data, 1999-2000; 2002 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Shared staff: Information packet, 2002 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Shared staff: Letters of support, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Shared staff: Letters, memos, and accompanying materials, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Shared staff: Letters to legislature, Office of Mental Health, DOB, and governor, 2000 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Shared staff: Long-term recommendations, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Shared staff: Planning, 2000; 2003 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Shared staff: Requests to NY State Legislature for restoration of shared staff funding, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Shared staff: Responses from legislature to Steve Dungan, 1999 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Shared staff: Responses to potential personnel reductions, 1995; 1998-1999 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Shared staff: Strategies to divert cuts, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Shared staff: Survey, 1999 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Shared staff: Survey- transitional, 2000 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Shared staff: Transition plan, 1999-2000 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Shared staff: Workgroup conference calls, 1999-2000 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - State comptroller's report on mental health planning services, 1993 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Statewide comprehensive plan for mental health services, 2002-2006, ca. 2001 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Technical Assistance Project success story, Undated (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Technical Assistance Project- Timetables, budget, agendas, 1998 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Temporary Assistance for Needy Families (TANF), Undated (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - "Transitions" training manual and handouts, 1999; Undated (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - "Transitions" training transparencies, Undated (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - T-shirt commemorating 30th anniversary of NYSCLMHD, 2006 (Oversized 1)
  - Welfare-to-Work Conference, 2000 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
- Newsletters, 1980-2008; Undated; 8; 0.6 cu. ft.
  The Conference began publishing its own newsletter in the early days of its existence, but most of the issues from the 1980s and 1990s are not included in this collection. Researchers will find a consistent run from 1979 through 1981, a few issues from 1993, 1994, and the late 1990s, then another consistent run from 2000 through 2008. There are also several issues of a newsletter published specially by the Conference chair.
  - January-December, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (8-Newsletters), Folder 2)
  - Mental Hygiene News, winter, 1993 (Box 1 (8-Newsletters), Folder 3)
  - Mental Hygiene News, winter, 1994 (Box 1 (8-Newsletters), Folder 4)
  - Conference Update, spring edition, 1996 (Box 1 (8-Newsletters), Folder 5)
  - Conference Update, special anniversary issue, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Newsletters), Folder 6)
  - January-February, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Newsletters), Folder 7)
  - Spring and October-December, 2001 (Box 1 (8-Newsletters), Folder 8)
  - January-December, 2002 (Box 1 (8-Newsletters), Folder 9)
  - Conference updates from chair, spring edition, 2002 (Box 1 (8-Newsletters), Folder 10)
  - January-December, 2003 (Box 1 (8-Newsletters), Folder 11)
  - January-December, 2004 (Box 1 (8-Newsletters), Folder 12)
  - January-December, 2005 (Box 1 (8-Newsletters), Folder 13)
  - January-December, 2006 (Box 2 (8-Newsletters), Folder 1)
  - January-December, 2007 (Box 2 (8-Newsletters), Folder 2)
  - January-December, 2008 (Box 2 (8-Newsletters), Folder 3)
  - Undated newsletters (Box 2 (8-Newsletters), Folder 4)
- Reports and Publications, 1982; 1989-2006; Undated; 9; 2.6 cu. ft.